Hello friends, my name is Ashish Patel and
how are you all? I hope you all are doing
well too. Friends, today I am going to discuss with you about
car insurance. My car
insurance is a very important
product. If you buy a car, then
you have to take car insurance along with the car.
Friends, there is a car insurance which is
compulsory in India. You will have to take car
insurance. Otherwise, if you
go on the road and you get caught by the traffic
police, then you will have to pay a challan.
Friends, what is the benefit of taking car insurance?
Therefore, car insurance
provides protection to your car
and
also provides protection to the person driving the car. It is
very important to insure your car before going out on the road.
What is the best car insurance
and what kind of benefits are there in taking car insurance.
First of all, if any kind of
car gets damaged, then the
insurance company will bear the repair cost of your car. If
someone else gets damaged through your car or dies, if it becomes
necessary, then the
insurance company will cover this cost as well.  If an
accident happens, you
get insurance cover for
cashless repair. If your vehicle gets seriously
damaged, even then
your insurance company gets it
repaired cashless. Types of
Restaurant Style Insurance: How many
types of insurance are there? Insurance is of
two types, one is comprehensive
insurance and the other is third party insurance, the
comprehensive of which means that
in this your own risk is covered,
your vehicle is covered, your
life insurance becomes important, MS Word becomes yours,
this happens many times in third party,
in third party it happens that if
you mix the time with someone on the road, then the
cover that
you have to give to him, the penalty that you have to pay, is
many times under third party insurance,
friends, before taking car insurance,
because there are many companies which offer different offers, there are different
schemes of different groups, there are different
benefits, so before taking car insurance,
you should
compare the insurance once,
you will get to know the benefit,
what is the premium of the insurance, what are the
terms and conditions of the insurance, what is the
percentage of the claim  It is
very important to look at all this from a company because the
insurance companies do
not cover all the details.
When you have to make an insurance claim,
then you realize that you do not know this condition score and you will
not get it at all.
Therefore, you should read and compare and get
insurance car insurance as per your needs.
Friends, I
cannot cover much details in the video, but
I will tell you that if you want to
know in more detail
how insurance is calculated,
which companies are there in insurance, what
offers are going on from INS company, then
I will tell you about a website named
Mortgage Loan Credit Card
Insurance Investment Offers to T&C. The
link of this website is given inside the description box. From there,
go to the Saffron Direct website.
Inside the website, you will get all the information,
where to buy, what is the price and what are the
benefits, which premium is the lowest, how to
calculate, you will get all the details. So,
this time before buying this, for this reason,
definitely visit this website once,
here you will definitely get the benefits,
one request and  If you liked this video, then there are
some benefits for you in knowing that
you should subscribe to this video,
like it, comment on it and
share it with your friends. Thank you, Namaskar.